system1research.com 2018-10-23

# Our Privacy & Cookie Policy - System1 Group

## Introduction

We are a marketing services agency using the websites [www.system1group.com](http://www.system1group.com/), [www.system1agency.com](http://www.system1agency.com/?__hstc=106808796.ecd6dde4156d2bad95c5991936805fe8.1491317391789.1512726913855.1512748726797.86&__hssc=106808796.1.1512748726797&__hsfp=32152925) and [www.system1research.com](http://www.system1research.com/?__hstc=106808796.ecd6dde4156d2bad95c5991936805fe8.1491317391789.1512726913855.1512748726797.86&__hssc=106808796.1.1512748726797&__hsfp=32152925). As a visitor of our website, a participant of our surveys or a recipient of our marketing emails, we assure you that we will never sell, rent or trade your personal information to any third party. This policy states when and why we may collect your personal information, how we would use it, when we may disclose it to others and how we would keep it confidential.

If you are an employee (or former employee) or applying for a job at System1, there is a separate policy applicable to the processing of your data. Please contact [HR@system1group.com](mailto:HR@system1group.com) for further details.

## Personal information – collection and use

Personal information means any information that could identify you e.g. your name, title, phone number, e-mail and mailing address.

We collect personal information when you complete our contact form or send us e-mails requesting information. We will use your personal information only to provide marketing services to our clients and to respond to questions you may have asked us.

We will keep this information only for as long as necessary and then we will delete it. If you wish, you may ask us to delete it sooner.

We may share your information outside System1 Agency and the System1 Group with our sub-contractors MAP, WNS, Toluna, FocusVision, Lambda or cQuest, but will do so only when necessary to enable us to deliver our creative agency or market research services or respond to any questions. We will first satisfy ourselves that they will keep your information confidential and will not use it for any purpose other than helping us to provide market research services to our clients. These firms have their own websites and apps, and have their own privacy and cookies policies which apply to visitors to their websites and users of their apps.

When you are participating in a healthcare study, we are required to pass details of adverse events or product complaints mentioned in your responses on to our client's drug safety department.

We will employ industry standard technology to ensure your information is secure and that we adhere to data protection laws. We will also ensure that any third party who we give access to your information does the same.

## Cookies

Our websites and applications use cookies to distinguish you from other users of the website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site. A cookie is a small data file placed on your device which makes your use more enjoyable and allows us to improve our services.

For more information on which cookies we use, please visit:

<https://knowledge.hubspot.com/articles/kcs_article/reports/what-cookies-does-hubspot-set-in-a-visitor-s-browser>

You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies, you may not be able to access all or parts of our site.

## Links to other websites

Any link from one of our websites to another is not covered by this Privacy Policy.

## Links to our website

You may link to our websites with our permission and provided you do so in a way that is fair and legal. We reserve the right to withdraw linking permission without notice.

## Access your personal information

You are entitled to access the personal information we hold about you. If your request is excessive we might charge an administrative fee at our discretion. Please email your request to [legal@system1group.com](mailto:legal@system1group.com).

## Updates and consent

Any changes we make to this policy in the future will be posted on this page. By using our websites, participating in online market research studies and using any other services we provide you confirm that you agree with these terms and consent to the collection and use of the information as outlined in this policy.

As a recipient of our newsletter or other marketing emails you will be able to unsubscribe at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” button or contacting marketing@system1group.com.

## Contact us

If you have any questions about this policy or want to know more on how we use the information we hold about you, please contact our legal department at [legal@system1group.com](mailto:legal@system1group.com).

Updated: 16 May 2018
